Welcome to Banking Process Guys, in today's
video we will learn how to insure
your bike and scooter from home through Go Digit Insurance Company. If
you have a scooter or a bike, then it is
mandatory to have at least third party insurance as per
law. So in this video I am going to tell you how to insure
your bike live through Go Digit Insurance Company.
So keep watching the video till the end.
If you are new to the channel and have visited for the first time, then
subscribe and
press the bell icon.
Talking about the claim settlement ratio of Go Digit Insurance Company, it is
97. The claim settlement
ratio shows us that out of the claims received by the company, how many claims have been
rejected by the company and
how many claims have been passed. And
basically, if the claim settlement ratio of any company is
above 95, then its claim
settlement ratio is considered quite good.
And friends, if you want to
insure your bike or
scooter through Go Digit, then I have given you the link on the i button.  It has been
provided or friends, you will
also get a link in the description of the video.
You can also complete the
insurance of your bike and scooter through a company sitting at home within
two minutes. There
is a link in the description of the video to insure your bike and scooter through Go Digit Insurance Company. Or
friends,
this kind of interface will open here
friends, you can see Digit Bike
Insurance Get Instant Policy in Minutes.
You have to enter the registration number of your bike like the
RC of the bike,
you have to enter the RC number of your scooter and
click on View Prices.
But before that, you can see Previous
Policy Expiry Not Expired
Expired If your policy has expired, then
you have to select on Expires. If it has not expired, then
click on Not Expired. When
you click on View Prices, then
this kind of interface will come in front of you. Here
friends, you can see on the top side
Claim Last Year No NCB Last Year Zero.
So to check the details of your bike, you have to simply go to
Your Vehicle.  You have to click on details.
You
can also see the details of your bike by clicking on your vehicle details.
If you want to make changes, you
can do that too. Friends, when you
do insurance, there will be two
types of covers on your display - comprehensive cover and
third party cover. If you
select comprehensive cover, then the damage to your bike is
also covered under it. If the bike gets damaged, then
you can claim for that too.
Friends, if you apply third party cover, then
you are given insurance coverage only for the third party.
You will
not get the IDV value here. There is a difference of a few rupees between third party insurance and
comprehensive insurance,
so you should compare it once. You can see that
we have
selected comprehensive cover. The
estimator price is coming at Rs. 776.
You have to select the duration. You can
see in the best deal. You can take 3 years insurance
or friends, if you want to do 1 year
insurance, then
you have to click on one year duration. After that,
friends, you will simply scroll down.
So you will get this kind of interface
Add Extra Coverage If you want to
add extra coverage, then you can see it on the display here
Personal Accidental Cover of 15
lakhs You are also offered personal accidental coverage here for ₹1 per month You will
get passenger cover PA cover for paid
driver These are three types of extra coverage,
if you want you can add it
Remember if you add this then your net
premium will also increase For now
friends if we have personal
accidental coverage then we will skip it
Scroll down and
click on continue As soon as
friends click on continue then here
automatically vehicle owner name will appear PIN
code will appear If you want to make changes in it then
you can also make changes
Enter your email ID Enter mobile number
Then friends previous policy details
If you have a previous policy
then enter its details otherwise you
can also block it Enter nominee name
What is the relation with the nominee,
you will have to enter it here Then
friends here  You can see the view
cost breakup. We have to pay a total of 915, so to make the
payment we simply have to click on Pay Now.
As soon as friends, we
click on Pay Now, then I
complete my payment in front of us. So I have
completed my payment by
entering the OTP. As soon as friends, our payment is
completed, then this kind of
interface will appear in front of us. Full owner name, address,
policy number, product, you can see
digit two wheeler package policy and friends,
you have to do KYC. To do KYC,
your by default mobile number will appear and
email ID will appear. You have to write the consent and
click on continue. As soon as
friends, we click on continue, then the
interface of KYC verification will appear in front of us. You can do it through OTP
and you
can also do KYC by uploading the document, so we will
upload the document here.
I clicked on By Document Upload here, so
I
upload the front size and reverse size of my Aadhar card here.
After uploading the document,
you simply click on submit.  You have to click
as soon as friends you click on submit
then you can see on the display
congratulations your vehicle has been insured successfully
our bike
insurance has been completed successfully now friends
simply you have to see the policy details if you want to
see the PDF of the policy then for this
you have to click on view policy document then
it will redirect you to
google.it more than 10 lakh people have
installed this app after
installing the app you have to login with the same mobile number
which you had mentioned in the insurance simply
friends you can see on the display here
your policy details will appear in the upcoming policy
and you can download it if you want
you
can also take a print out by downloading the PDF
keep it with you your bike scooter
insurance is done friends by
following this process you can complete the insurance of
your bike and scooter through Go Digit Insurance Company in an easy way
sitting at home within
5 minutes if
you liked this video if you liked it
So like and share it
with your friends and subscribe to our channel Banking
Process so that you
get information about such videos first.